<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">HowAreU</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <!-- Home Fragment -->
    <string name="home_to_do_list">To do:</string>
    <string name="home_activity">Activity:</string>
    <string name="home_journal">Journal(optional):</string>


    <string name="very_sad">Very Sad</string>
    <string name="sad">Sad</string>
    <string name="neutral">Neutral</string>
    <string name="happy">Happy</string>
    <string name="very_happy">Very Happy</string>


    <string name="stats_mood_count">Mood Count:</string>
    <string name="stats_mood_count_percentage">Mood Count:</string>
    <string name="stats_mood_summary">Mood Summary:</string>
    <string name="stats_mood_summary_m">Mood for the month:</string>

    <string name="about_us" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">Welcome to our app, where we strive to help you achieve a blissful lifestyle by prioritizing good mental health. Our mission is to help you achieve and maintain optimal mental well-being by providing you with the tools and resources you need to monitor and manage your moods and activities.\n\nWe understand that mental health is a complex and multifaceted issue that affects people differently. That's why we've developed a comprehensive mood and activity monitoring system that can be tailored to your specific needs and preferences.\n\nHow are U is designed to make it easy for you to track your daily activities, mood changes, and other important factors that can affect your mental health. By collecting and analyzing this data, we can identify patterns and trends that may indicate the need for intervention or support.\n\nSo whether you're dealing with anxiety, depression, or just trying to maintain a healthy work-life balance, our app is here to support you every step of the way. We believe that by taking an active role in your mental health, you can achieve a happier, more fulfilling life.</string>
</resources>